http://www.houseforanartlover.co.uk/privacy-policy

Basket (0)|E-Newsletter|Blog|Search
About What is House for an Art Lover?History of the HouseAround the HouseCharles Rennie MackintoshBlogYour Event
LocationsMackintosh SuiteThe ViewMeeting RoomsFor Weddings...Weddings at House for an Art LoverWedding PackagesPlanning AdvicePrevious CelebrationsWedding Venue 3D TourWedding Venue 3D Tour 2For Business...Your Event at House for an Art LoverBespoke Corporate SessionsRoom Layouts, Menus & PricingFor Private Occasions...Hosting at House for an Art LoverRoom Layouts, Menus & PricingFunerals & Memorials Visit Explore the HouseOpening Times & Admission PricesArt Lover's CaféArt Lover's ShopTravel Information & AccessibilityArts Studio PavilionColourful ExpressionsWhat's On HighlightsSupport UsContact Contact Us
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
MAY 2018
House for an Art Lover (HAL) , also known as , HAL Commercial Co Ltd currently hold some of your personal data which we will continue to hold and process through the condition of legitimate interests in order to provide you services relating to hospitality.
TYPES OF DATA
HAL hold any data that you have provided directly during the course of legitimate business dealings plus any information you have provided to us directly including and not limited to: - name, contact details, personal/business addresses, postcode, personal/business telephone numbers including mobile, personal/business email addresses and supporting data when required for service purposes, company finance details and credit checks.
RECRUITMENT
HAL is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy explains the steps we take to ensure that personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) is kept secure and confidential. We will process Personal Data that you provide to us solely for recruiting purposes (including by potentially contacting referees provided in your CV). If you provide HAL with information about third parties, we will assume that the third party in question has given you permission to do so and HAL to collect, to process and to transfer their Personal Data to the same extent as your own.
In reviewing your CV, there are some circumstances where we may disclose your Personal
Data including :-
To HAL employees who are involved in our recruitment and selection processes, for example, relevant managers and human resources
To the extent necessary or appropriate to government agencies, advisers and other third parties in order to comply with applicable laws.
If we do not place you in a position within HAL, your Personal Data will be kept for a period of maximum 1 years ( or less if required by applicable laws ) from the date of receipt of your CV, after which time it will be removed, or removed earlier upon your request. By submitting your Personal Data you agree that you have read, understood and accept this CV Privacy Statement.
If you wish to amend any of your Personal Data or if you have any other questions in connection with the processing of your Personal Data, please send your request to
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
CCTV
CCTV is used on the premises for the purpose of public safety and crime prevention/ detection. Footage collected from the CCTV is recorded 24 hours a day and is kept for 31 calendar days when it is automatically deleted. CCTV recordings are password protected and only available to authorized personnel.
PURPOSE OF PROCESSING
HAL securely stores your data on a secure encrypted server. HAL will continue to process your data in order to manage the hospitality service in which you have employed the business, including and not limited to; event and wedding bookings, art class bookings, café reservations, sending customer invoices, customer statements and supplier remittances via email. HAL will, on some occasions, process your data for internal reporting reasons such as reviewing the number of event bookings in a certain period of time. These reports will not be shared with third parties but anonymized reports may be discussed and shared (not including any specific Personal Data)
DATA RETENTION
HAL will retain your personal data only for as long as is necessary. Different laws require us to keep different data for different periods of time.
SHARING DATA
HAL will not share your data with any third parties unless you have given explicit written consent, this consent can be withdrawn at any time.
SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
HAL house your data on a secured server, encrypted and backed up, backups are held offsite at a secure location. All of the software used to process and store your data is password protected and is accessed by authorized employees only. Should there be a data breach this will be investigated and reported to the Information Commissioners Office (ICO) within 72 hours.
YOUR RIGHTS – RECTIFICATION AND ERASURE
You have the right to choose who holds your data. If you do not wish HAL to hold your data, you have the right to have any personal data we hold on your corrected or deleted. If this is the case, please communicate this in writing to: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it., providing details of the data you wish to be corrected OR if you wish to have your data deleted. We will then respond within 30 days of receipt or request.
SUBJECT ACCESS REQUEST
If you wish to access the data we hold on you please email:
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. outlining the specific request and we will respond to you within 30 days of receipt of SAR
WITHDRAW CONSENT
Where you have consented to HAL processing your personal data you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time, please communicate this in writing to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
COMPLAINTS
If you wish to complain about how HAL has processed your data or how we have dealt with any of your requests regarding your data, please contact the Information Commissioners Office complaint helpline on 0303 123 1113.
Terms & Conditions :: >Privacy Policy :: Site Map
AboutWhat is House for an Art Lover?History of the HouseAround the HouseCharles Rennie MackintoshBlogYour EventLocationsMackintosh SuiteThe ViewMeeting RoomsFor Weddings...Weddings at House for an Art LoverWedding PackagesPlanning AdvicePrevious CelebrationsWedding Venue 3D TourWedding Venue 3D Tour 2For Business...Your Event at House for an Art LoverBespoke Corporate SessionsRoom Layouts, Menus & PricingFor Private Occasions...Hosting at House for an Art LoverRoom Layouts, Menus & PricingFunerals & Memorials VisitExplore the HouseOpening Times & Admission PricesArt Lover's CaféArt Lover's ShopTravel Information & AccessibilityArtsStudio PavilionWhat's OnHighlightsSupport UsContactContact Us
